Guide to the Ralph E. Griswold Collection, GWSM, Inc., 1912-1988 AIS.2001.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Flat File Material, undated; V.; (Oversized)
  - Oversized Flat File Print Material, 1.
    - Allen's Oak and Gates: Villa Medici photograph, Firenza Artistica, and "Caryatides of the Erechteion" print, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    - Adolph Dupres Cabin: front and rear view, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 7)
    - First House Built in Cincinnati, OH: perspective, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 8)
    - Private Residents: Roy A. Hunt residence Perspective, B. D. Phillips residence Perspective, and Perspective of unknown residence, 1944 (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 9)
    - Franklin Delano Roosevelt Memorial: Plan on art paper, Elevation on vellum, Perspective on trace; Plan on trace, Rendered plan, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 10)
    - Richard K. Mellon Mountain Vista improvements, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 11)
    - Shadyside Presbyterian Church: Perspective on Chapel entrance garden, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 12)
    - Coraopolis Borough Park: Proposed swimming pool perspective, Proposed all-purpose athletic field perspective, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 13)
    - Chatham Village: Landscape plan for first unit, Plan of landscape development and Plan of landscape development, 1939 (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 14)
    - Richeyville Recreation Building: Landscape improvements perspective, 1947 (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 15)
    - John Sephus Mack Community Center: Memorial Entrance perspective, Memorial Entrance perspective revised, Picnic Shelter perspective and Pool, 1946 (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 16)
    - Vestaburg School: Landscape improvements rendering, Vestaburg Recreation Building: Proposed planting rendering and Proposed planting rendering, 1947 (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 17)
    - Fox Chapel Country Club: Pool perspective, 1930 (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 18)
    - Mr. & Mrs. Charles M. DuPuy: Front and rear perspectives, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 19)
    - Charles F. Chubb Memorial, McConnell's Mill State Park: preliminary study, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 20)
    - Lion's Club of America, California Borough: Recreational study plan, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 21)
    - Beaver Area Joint School District High School: Study, Site no. 1 expanded perspective and Study, Site no. 2 perspective, 1954 (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 22)
    - Parks: Urban playgrounds perspective and National perspective, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 23)
    - Mr. H.B. Higgins Estate: Perspective, Plan and seven photographs, 1932 (Map-case 5, Drawer 1, Folder 24)
    - Watercolors: Mr. & Mrs. John W. Lawrence Estate, Hartwood Acres, 1931 (Map-case 5, Drawer 2, Folder 25)
    - B.D. Phillips Residence: three photographs, two Inner Court rendering prints and Inner Court perspective, 1944 (Map-case 5, Drawer 2, Folder 26)
    - Anzio-Nettuno Military Cemetery: Sixteen photographs, Cover of V.F.W. Magazine, two perspectives with plan, Rendered plan, Aerial photograph, Proposed tree planting perspective and Axial view perspective, 1950-1956 (Map-case 5, Drawer 2, Folder 27)
    - Mr. & Mrs. Roy A. Hunt Garden: four photographs, walled garden elevation perspective and plan, 1944 (Map-case 5, Drawer 2, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous Photostats, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 2, Folder 29)
    - Bellevue Park: three aerial view perspective photostats, 3 proposed Memorial Entrance perspective photostats, Park under construction (aerial photograph) and two Dedication pamphlets, 1951 (Map-case 5, Drawer 2, Folder 30)
    - A.K. Wright Memorial, Hillcrest Cemetery perspective and plan, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 2, Folder 31)
    - Mr. & Mrs. Cyrus H. McCormick: Thirteen photostats and three photographs, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 2, Folder 32)
    - Agora Excavations: eight photographs, a Plan of Restoration of Stoa, Postcard of west side of Agora model, Map of ancient Greece, Bench perspective, Reconstruction of Stoa of Attalos, Map of Attica, Map of Modern Athens and Tourist map of Greece, 1950-1956 (Map-case 5, Drawer 2, Folder 33)
    - Parks: Burgess Park swimming pool and bath house perspective, Titusville Park Aerial view perspective, and Recreation park and swimming pool pamphlet, 1949 (Map-case 5, Drawer 2, Folder 34)
    - Residences: Mr. & Mrs. H. J. Stringer, Jr. Residence: Perspective, Mr. & Mrs. Morton Aronson Residence: Plan, Mr. & Mrs. Harton S. Semple Residence: Terrace perspective, Ed Magee Residence: "Baywind" perspective, Mr. & Mrs. Paul Ever Residence: Entrance perspective, Mrs. John Fazer Residence: Townhouse, Mr. & Mrs. Oliver Blair Residence: Perspective, Mr. & Mrs. Blair Shiller Residence: Garden perspective, 1930-1945 (Map-case 5, Drawer 2, Folder 35)
    - Fox Chapel Country Club: Interior Court perspective, Interior Court perspective and three photographs, 1930 (Map-case 5, Drawer 2, Folder 36)
    - Griswold Certificates: American Academy of Rome, Cornell University, Papal Blessing & Greek Recognition, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 2, Folder 37)
    - Allegheny County Club: Plan, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 2, Folder 38)